女士们先生们  关键的时刻即将到来
Ladies and gentlemen, the moment is almost upon us.
在誉满全球的训狗师弗兰斯科·普拉尔
As world-renowned trainer Francisco Pilar
最后一次审视决赛选手们时
takes one last look at the finalists,
只有一个疑问悬而未决
only one question remains.
谁将获得本年度选秀的第一名
Who will be this year's best in show?
我正站在观众席中
I'm here in the audience...
和电视真人秀明星凯·卡普奇诺
with reality TV star Kay Cappuccio
及她的经纪人兼男友雷吉·斯达一起
and her manager and boyfriend-- Reggie Starr.
凯  你和雷吉什么时候结婚呢
Kay, when are you and Reggie getting married?
婚礼会在节目中进行吗
Will it happen on the show?
我只想和我所有的粉丝们问声好
I just wanna say hi to all my fans out there
也提醒大家下个月
and remind them that next month,
我的新香水就要上市了
my new scent hits stores--
凯·卡普奇诺之罪恶的欢愉
Kay Cappuccio's Guilty Pleasure.
确保他的罪名是渴望得到你
Make sure he's guilty of wanting you.
弗兰斯科准备好要公布他的决定了
Francisco is ready to reveal his decision.
第一名
One.
第二名
Two.
第三名
Three.
结果已经揭晓  各位
And there you have it, folks.
本年度桑福尔养狗场狗狗选秀的第一名
This year's Sunfare Kennel best in show
就是独一无二...
is the one, the only...
巴顿斯
Buttons?
你有朋友叫巴顿斯  是人类的朋友吗
You have a friend named Buttons, a human friend?
是她妈妈小时候给取的昵称  延续了下来
Her mom called her that when she was little, and it stuck.
现在该她流芳百世了
And now so is she.
巴顿斯和我因为被斯坦福所拒而成了朋友
Buttons and I bonded over being rejected from Stanford,
实际上  我们申请了很多相同的学校
In fact, we applied to a lot of the same schools,
所以我们打算这周末去一些校园逛逛
so we were planning to visit a few campuses together this weekend,
来一段公路旅行
make a road trip out of it.
好吧  这个
Okay, whoa.
你们要住哪里  谁来开车
Where are you staying? Who's driving?
谁做你们的监护人
And who is chaperoning?
我们会开走你的法拉利
We were going to take your Ferrari
然后和在克雷格广告网上认识的男生鬼混
and hook up with some boys we met on Craigslist.
-这可不好笑  -亲爱的
- Not cool. - Honey,
别这么扫兴嘛
don't be such a killjoy.
我想巴顿斯的妈妈是会一起去的
I'm sure Buttons' mother is going along.
是的  而且她是非常有责任心的人
She is and she's very responsible.
除了在挑选昵称时
Yeah, except when it comes to picking nicknames.
如果你愿意  我会让达顿太太
Look, if you want, I could have Mrs. Dutton
在来接我时和你见一面的
stop by to meet you when she picks me up.
很好  我觉得这样可...
Yeah, I think that'd be o--
她姓达顿
Her last name is Dutton?
你朋友名叫巴顿斯·达顿
Your friend's name is Buttons Dutton?
这真是太不幸了
That is unfortunate.
这又怎么了
What's so wrong with that?
得了吧  这就好比叫我卡摔尔
Oh, come on. It'd be like calling me Rastle
或者卡穗尔
or Tassel...
卡塞尔·无忧  你好
or No-hassle Castle. Hey.
不  我只想说明一个观点
No, I was just making a point.
求求你别这么叫我
Please don't call me that.
死者叫弗兰斯科·普拉尔  是选秀的评委
The victim is Francisco Pilar, judge of the dog show.
我们是在他的化妆间发现他的
We found him here in his dressing room.
他的现金  钱包  手表都在
He still had cash on him, plus his wallet, phone,
还有一张类似门卡的东西
and a key card of some kind.
死因和看上去的一样吗
Is the cause of death what it looks like?
没错  有人用皮带绕在他脖子上用力拉扯
Yep. Someone put a leash around his neck and pulled.
你们确定死亡时间了吗
Do you guys have an estimated time of death?
-我拼凑出了一个时间段...  -不好意思
- I put together a window-- - Excuse me?
你现在是要做我的工作了吗
You're doing my job now?
我还不知道你是医学院毕业的
I didn't know you went to medical school.
不过请说吧  埃斯波西托医生
But go ahead, Dr. Esposito.
最后见到弗兰斯科活着的人
Okay. The last guy to see Francisco alive,
是在5点15离开房间
uh, left this room at 5:15
去帮他拿晚餐的
to go get him some dinner.
接着格林先生二十分钟后就发现他死了
Then Mr. Greene found him like this 20 minutes later.
好的  谢了
Okay. Thanks.
-你好  -你好  我是亚当·格林
- Hi. - Hi. Adam Greene.
我是桑福尔选秀的组织者
I'm the Sunfare show organizer.
格林先生  你对死者弗兰斯科了解如何
Mr. Greene, how well did you know our victim--Francisco?
弗兰斯科做我们的评委快二十年了
Uh, Francisco's been our judge for almost two decades.
他比任何人都在乎这些狗
No one cared about dogs more than he did.
他有可以提供情况的家人吗
Did he have any family that we could talk to?
罗亚尔就是他的家人
Royal was his family.
这狗真帅
Oh, that's a handsome pooch.
弗兰斯科非常爱它
Francisco loved him very much.
事实上
The truth is,
他和狗相处得比和狗主人还好
he got along with dogs a lot better than their owners.
所以他精通狗语
So dog whisperer, check.
而不擅长人语
People whisperer, not so much.
他和狗主人之间有矛盾吗
Did he have any problems with any of the owners?
你在暗示什么
What are you suggesting?
他在选出选秀第一名后的
Just that he was killed about a half an hour
半小时左右就被杀害了
after he gave out best in show.
我承认  选秀狗的主人有时会很激动
I'll admit, show dog owners can be passionate people,
但不会激动到这种程度
but not to this extent.
有人把那条皮带缠在他的脖子上了
Somebody wrapped that leash around his neck.
我们需要一份包括
We'll need a list of the names
所有参赛者以及可能进出
of all of the contestants, along with anyone
这个房间的人员的名单
that might have had access to this room.
没问题
Of course.
这不是弗兰斯科·普拉尔的狗嘛
Isn't this Francisco Pilar's dog?
是的  这就是罗亚尔
Yes, that's Royal.
我们觉得最好还是让它离开那房间
We thought it best to keep him out of the room.
它干嘛这样做
Why is he doing that?
我们发现它时  他正在尸体旁边
He was doing the same thing by the body
做同样的动作
when we found him.
也许是他表示悲痛的方式吧
Maybe some sort of grieving process.
我去给你写名单
I'll get you that list of names.
谢了
Thank you.
所以凶案发生时
So the dog was at the crime scene
这狗正在犯罪现场
at the time of the murder.
你想让我们干嘛  带它去问话吗
What do you want us to do, bring him in for questioning?
我只是想说  人类最好的朋友
I'm just saying, would man's best friend
会眼睁睁看着它的主人被袭击吗
stand idly by while his master was attacked?
要是它真的去干预了
And if he did intervene,
也许它还能留下点DNA或微量迹证
maybe he got D.N.A. or trace evidence on him
帮我们找到凶手
that could lead to our killer.
我可能找到了一条线索
May have a lead of my own.
有个输掉了比赛的选手刚递交了
One of the losing contestants just filed this appeal
对弗兰斯科裁决的上诉  一个叫大卫·赫南德的人
of Francisco's decision-- a guy named David Hernand.
他们说他气愤到
They said he was so angry
脑门上的血管一跳一跳的
that the vein in his forehead was visibly throbbing.
显然  狗狗选秀就是这家伙的全部人生
Apparently, dog shows are this guy's whole life.
我对弗兰斯科的死感到不安吗
Was I upset about Francisco's death?
当然
Sure.
但他对选秀第一名的裁决更令我生气
I was more upset about his choice for best in show.
那缎带明明该是我家麦克斯的
That ribbon belonged to my Max.
赫南德先生  你5点15到35分时
Mr. Hernand, can you account for your whereabouts
人在何处
between 5:15 and 5:35?
我就在我的修整处这里
Yeah, I was right here at my grooming station
填写我的上诉  我可没杀他好吗
filing my appeal-- oh, I didn't kill him. Okay?
鉴于他干的各种勾当
Given everything he was into,
我觉得他是自作自受
I'd say, he brought it on himself.
他干了什么勾当呢
And what exactly was he into?
有传闻说
Well, rumor has it...
他收受了贿赂
he was on the take.
你是说  有人为左右选秀而贿赂他了吗
Are you saying, he was taking bribes to fix dog shows?
狗狗选秀的赌盘  可是一笔大生意
Betting on dog shows-- it's a big business.
他被发现和一些非常可疑的人在一起
And he was seen with some pretty shady characters.
一些和拉斯维加斯有关联的人
People with ties to Vegas.
这可是很严重的指控
That's a serious allegation.
你有证据吗
Do you have any proof to back it up?
你想要证据
You want proof?
那就是弗兰斯科选出的第一名
That's who Francisco selected best in show.
看看那杂种狗的样子
Just look at that mutt.
再看看我的麦克斯
Now back to my Max.
再看看那杂种狗
Now the mutt.
这就是我的证据
That's all the proof I need.
真的吗  狗狗选秀上有大赌注吗
Really? There's big money riding on dog shows?
说起来其实挺精明的
It's actually kind of ingenious.
人人都小心翼翼审视着足球赛
You know, everyone's got football, basketball,
篮球赛和赛马
horse racing under a microscope,
试图找到违规的蛛丝马迹
looking for the slightest hint of impropriety.
谁会关注狗狗选秀呢
Who's looking at dog shows?
我会让莱恩追查这事
I'm gonna have Ryan look into it
和赫南德的不在场证明的
along with Hernand's alibi.
不管你们在说什么  都可以放一放了
Whatever you're talking about, it can wait.
女士  请告诉贝克特探长
Ma'am, please tell detective Beckett
你之前所说的话
what you told me?
选秀结束后我在后台
I was backstage after the show
看到一个女人离开弗兰斯科的化妆间
when I saw a woman leave Francisco's dressing room.
你能描述她的样子吗
Can you describe her?
不止如此
Even better.
我用手机拍下了一段视频
I took a video with my phone.
尽管她带着兜帽和墨镜
She was wearing a hood and sunglasses,
我还是一眼就认出了她
but I recognized her instantly.
是凯·卡普奇诺
It was Kay Cappuccio.
那个电视真人秀明星吗
The reality television star?
看看拍摄时间
Check the time stamp.
正处于凶杀时间范围内
Right in the middle of our time-of-death window.
我不能理解的是
Here's what I don't get--
为什么凯·卡普奇诺要杀弗兰斯科·普拉尔呢
Why would Kay Cappuccio want to kill Francisco Pilar?
而我不能理解的是  这个女人
Here's what I don't get-- how does this woman
拥有自己的香水品牌
have her own perfume line,
公寓外驻守着成群结队的狗仔队
an army of paparazzi outside of her apartment,
推特上有上万的粉丝
millions of twitter followers,
上了几十本杂志封面
dozens of magazine covers,
却并没有任何真正的才华能解释她的名气
all with no discernable talent to account for it?
更让人费解的是  为什么她的所有照片
Even more perplexing, why in almost every photo
几乎都是这个造型
is she posed like this?
大家别激动
Oh, guys.
抱歉  没有拍照时间
Sorry. No time for photos.
好吧  只拍一张
Okay, maybe just one.
请微笑  看这边
Smile.
这人根本不是杰森·贝特曼
Hey, that's not Jason Bateman.
好老的梗
That's getting old.
你们应该是软饮公司的人吧
You two must be the, uh, soft drink people, right?
实际上不是  我们是纽约警局的
Actually, no. We are NYPD.
我们来询问凯·卡普奇诺几个问题
We're here to speak with Kay Cappuccio.
抱歉
Oh, my bad.
不如你们先去那边稍坐一会儿
Why don't you just grab a squat right over there?
你说什么
Excuse me?
菲比会为你们奉上枸杞果汁
Phoebe will bring you a goji berry juice.
你知道吗  我有更好的想法
You know what? I think I have a better idea.
所有人听着  休息五分钟
Everybody, take five.
等一下
Whoa. Hold on a second.
凯·卡普奇诺可没有五分钟可休息
Kay Cappuccio doesn't have five to spare.
那就十五到二十分钟
How about 15 to 20?
那个枸杞果汁听上去很不错
And that goji berry juice sounds delightful.
是的  我认识弗兰斯科
Sure, I knew Francisco.
我雇他为我的狗狗做一个两周的行为训练
I hired him to do two weeks of behavior training with my dog.
不久后我们的节目将会继续拍摄
Our show's gonna start shooting again soon,
但是洛丽塔的进攻性有点强
and Lolita has some minor aggression issues
我想对此改善一下
I wanted taken care of.
你是说这个小可爱吗
This little charmer?
难以相信...
I find it hard to believe--
我猜你是去要回你的钱吧
I assume you asked for your money back.
我还没有支付过
I never paid him.
他只训了几天  就在昨天早上
He brought her back yesterday morning
把她还回来了
after just a few days,
说他不愿意为我工作
said he didn't want to work with me.
你们问完了吗
So are we done here?
我还要试服装  几个认证会谈
'cause I have fittings, a couple of endorsement meetings,
走几场红毯
like three red carpets I have to show up at--
我有目击证人看到你出现在凶案现场
And I've got a witness that places you at the murder scene,
坐下
so sit down.
好吧
Sure.
你为什么在昨晚的选秀之后
Now why did you go to see Francisco
去见弗兰斯科
after the dog show last night?
我希望听他解释
I wanted an explanation as to why
他为什么不愿意训练洛丽塔
he wouldn't train Lolita.
那他怎么说
And what did he tell you?
我实在不愿意谈论这个问题
I would so much rather not go into it.
我们掌握了一段你离开弗兰斯科化妆间的视频
We've got a video of you leaving Francisco's dressing room
时间恰好落在谋杀时间范围内
right around the time of the murder.
所以是否谈论这个问题由不得你选择
So not going into it is not an option.
好吧
Fine.
我们什么也没说
We didn't talk about anything,
因为那时他已经死了
because he was already dead.
-你发现了尸体  -是的
- You found the body? - Yeah.
但是你没有报警
And you didn't call 9-1-1?
没有  但我一回到车上立刻就报警了
No, I did as soon as I got into the limo.
无伤大雅  不算犯法  对吧
No harm, no foul, right?
但是你逃离了犯罪现场
You fled a crime scene.
好吧
All right.
你有没有听过这句话
Have you heard the phrase
"没有绝对的负面报道"
"There's no such thing as bad press"?
但是如果被拍到跟尸体在一起
Having your picture taken with a dead guy
就是这句话的例外
is the exception.
我需要时刻注意自己的形象
I have to be so careful with my image.
我的形象就是我的全部资本
My image is all that I have.
是啊  我们刚才也在讨论这个问题
Yeah. No, we were just talking about that.
卡普奇诺小姐
Ms. Cappuccio,
弗兰斯科把狗带回来给你时
when Francisco brought your dog back,
有没有什么异常的表现
was he acting unusual at all?
我没有看到他
Oh, I didn't see him.
他来的时候正是我上午十点的健身时间
He showed up in the middle of my 10:00 a.m. workout.
当时我在  是我接收了洛丽塔
I was here, so I took Lolita.
你没说错  他当时的表现是有点奇怪
But you're right. The guy was acting weird.
他一直重复  "她究竟为谁卖命
He kept saying, "Who is she working for?
我知道她背后肯定有人"
I know she's working for somebody."
他看上去真的很疑神疑鬼
He seemed really paranoid.
你知道他在说什么吗
Do you have any idea what he was talking about?
毫无头绪
No clue.
所以我才决定上门问清楚
That's why I went to go talk with him.
好的  我想我们问完了
Okay. Well, I guess, then, we are done...
暂时而言
for now.
但是你要保持随传随到
Just, uh, stay available for questioning.
天哪  我还可能消失吗
Oh, my god. Like I'm gonna go anywhere?
我每迈出一步都会有成千上万的镜头对准我
I can't take one step without a million people taking my picture.
为什么有人
Well, it's no mystery
不愿与凯共事已经不是个谜题
why someone wouldn't want to be in business with Kay.
但是为什么弗兰斯科会以为她在为别人做事
But why did Francisco think that she was working for someone?
尤其是她整个人生根本就是什么事都不做
Especially since her whole life is about not working.
他为什么对她这么疑神疑鬼
And what made him so paranoid about her?
或许他有不可告人的秘密  看上去
Maybe he had something to hide. Looks like there might be
流言并不全然是假的  比赛可能真有猫腻
some truth to those rumors that the fix was in.
没错  我查了弗兰斯科的财务情况
Yeah, I've been going through Francisco's financials.
单就去年  他有几笔现金存款记录
He made a bunch of cash deposits over the last year--
每笔一万元
10 grand a pop.
我们回去查看了他近期裁判过的几场选秀
So we went back and looked at the last few shows he judged.
死者似乎对高风险参赛者情有独钟
Our boy had a thing for long shots.
昨天桑福尔选秀的冠军在维加斯赌场上的
The line at Vegas on yesterday's Sunfare winner
赔率达到五十比一
was 50 to 1.
真是个不被看好的狗
A real underdog.
还有一点说不通的是
Well, what doesn't make any sense is,
如果他确实收受贿赂  为什么要杀了他
if he was taking the bribes, why would they kill him?
或许他想要退出
Maybe he wanted out
或者开价提高了
or more money.
他的行程本上写着每周会与一个理疗师
His calendar said he had weekly appointments
见一次面  帕蒂·贝克医生
with a therapist-- a dr. Patty Barker.
他死那天刚好有过一次会面
They had a session the day he died.
或许她能为我们解开一些迷惑
Maybe she can fill in some gaps.
那把她带回来询问
Okay, let's bring her in.
给你们带了一个小客人
Brought you guys a little visitor.
看这是谁来了  罗亚尔来了
Oh, look who it is. It's Royal.
瞧瞧你  你真可爱呀
Look at you. You're adorable.
是的  可爱极了
Okay, adorable.
我们从他嘴里取样  希望找到人类的DNA
We swabbed his mouth for human D.N.A.,
但是我不抱太大希望
but I don't have high hopes.
即使之前真有  他分泌那么多唾液...
Even if there were some, all that slobbering--
大概早就咽下去了
it's probably long gone.
我们该拿罗亚尔怎么办
Hey, what are we gonna do with Royal?
我是说  弗兰斯科没有任何亲属
I mean, Francisco didn't have any family.
我真不忍心打电话给动物控制部门
I didn't have the heart to call animal control.
珍妮有个朋友开了一家动物援救机构
Jenny's friend runs a rescue.
或者  我们可以把他留在这儿
Or... we could keep him here at the precinct.
我是说  我们可以有个吉祥物嘛
I mean, we could use a mascot.
我以为你就是我们的吉祥物
I thought that's what you were.
你  你说什么
That--what's that?
伙计  你刚才说什么
What's that, buddy?
埃斯波西托的幽默感掉进井里爬不出来了
Esposito's sense of humor fell down a well and can't get out?
拜托
Please.
好吧  但是只能留到给他找到新家之前
Okay, fine, but only until we find him a suitable home.
那你们得搞清楚他吃哪种狗粮
Then you better find out what kind of food he eats,
因为我喂给他的他碰都没碰一下
because he's not touching the stuff I put out.
弗兰斯科家里肯定有
Well, there's gotta be some food for him
他爱吃的狗粮
at Francisco's place.
-你们谁去跑一趟吧  -去拿狗粮吗
- Who wants to make a run for it? - To go get dog food?
-卡塞尔  -莱恩  -埃斯波西托
- Castle. - Ryan. - Esposito.
那我们就像男人一样的解决吧
Well... Shall we settle this like men?
好的
All right.
三局两胜
Two outta three?
他做我病人已经很多年了
Oh, he's been my patient for years.
只要他的行程允许我们就会见面
I see him whenever his travel allows for it.
贝克医生  他正在处理什么样的问题
Dr. Barker, what kind of issues was he dealing with?
他有没有表现出疑心病的迹象
Did he ever exhibit signs of paranoia?
没有  只是偶尔的抑郁
No. The occasional bout of depression,
导致了他的自卑
which then led to low self-esteem,
又导致了暴食
Which led to binge eating, uh...
饮食问题
An eating problem?
还真是看不出来
You wouldn't know it to look at him.
他的饮食习惯非常可怕
Oh, his diet was horrible.
哦  垃圾桶里的残羹剩饭
Oh, scraps from the garbage,
死鸟  甚至是他自己的粪便
dead birds, even his own feces.
我们这里说的不是弗兰斯科吧
We're not talking about Francisco here, are we?
你以为我是弗兰斯科的心理医生吗
Oh, y-you thought I was Francisco's therapist?
天呐  不  不
H-heavens no, no.
我的病人是罗亚尔
My patient is Royal.
我是一个犬类治疗师
Well, I am a canine therapist.
如果让我治疗人的话就太疯狂了
Be pretty crazy for me to treat people.
人  那就太疯狂了
People? That would be crazy.
贝克医生
Uh, Dr. Bark--
呃  贝克女士  罗亚尔最后一次来的时候
Mrs. Barker, how did Francisco seem to you
弗兰斯科看上去怎么样
at Royal's last appointment?
实际上  他取消了
Well, actually, he canceled it.
他有说为什么吗
Did he say why?
只是说他突然有点事
Just that something had come up
他必须马上赶去个地方
and he had to be somewhere in a hurry.
好吧  这些
Okay, that's...
实际上很有帮助
actually helpful.
那好  谢谢你
Well... Well, um, thank you.
如果还有其他事的话我们会联系你的
We'll contact you if we need anything further.
罗亚尔现在怎么样了
How-- how is Royal doing?
他是不是真的在犯罪现场
Is it true that he was at the crime scene,
目睹了这场谋杀
that he witnessed the murder?
是的  我们是这么认为的
We think so, yes.
他也许看到了什么
There may be things he saw,
试图告诉我们关于凶杀的事情
things he's trying to communicate about the crime.
如果你能让我见他
If you let me see him,
我可以试着弄清楚他都知道什么
I can try to find out what he knows.
要知道  弗兰斯科对她很有信心
You know, Francisco had a lot of faith in her.
也许值得花点时间
Might be worth a few minutes.
你的时间的话  没问题
Of your time, sure.
我去带他过来
I'll get him.
找到的狗粮足够罗亚尔吃上好一阵子的了
Found enough dog food to keep Royal fat and happy for a while.
还找到了点别的东西
Found something else tasty, too.
电子窃听器扫描仪
Electronic bug sweeper.
看上去挺新的
Looks new.
用来探测窃听设备的吗
To detect eavesdropping devices?
不管他是不是疑神疑鬼
Paranoia or not,
弗兰斯科认为自己被人监视了
Francisco thought he was under surveillance.
弗兰斯科担心他被窃听了
Okay, so Francisco was worried that he was being bugged.
还有昨天大概上午十点左右
And then yesterday, somewhere around 11:00 AM,
他突然出门  也是大约这个时段  凯的助手
he runs off, right around the time that Kay's assistant
说他变得疑神疑鬼的时候
said that he started acting paranoid.
几个小时之后  他就被谋杀了
Then a few hours later, he's murdered.
那么他到底去了哪里
So then where the hell did he go?
要知道  我们证物里有弗兰斯科的手机
You know, we've got Francisco's cell phone in evidence.
如果定位系统开着
If the GPS was turned on,
那么也许能告诉我们他去过哪里
it might tell us exactly where he went.
是啊  没错
Yes, that's right.
我知道
I know.
我知道的
I know you are.
这个可怜的小家伙被吓坏了
Oh, the poor thing is just traumatized.
你们找到他的时候他是什么样的
How was he when you found him?
他们说他在刨地
Uh, they said that he was pawing at the ground.
桑福尔的人说这是丧亲的表现
Uh, the man from Sunfare said that was a sign of bereavement?
罗亚尔  罗亚尔
Royal, Royal,
看我在做什么
look at what I'm doing.
没错
That's right.
我就知道
I-I know it is.
他在试图告诉你一些东西
He was trying to tell you something,
很重要的东西
something important.
真的吗  你这样就能看出来
Really? You can tell all that from...
罗亚尔  看着我
Royal, look at me.
我知道  我知道你很伤心
I know. I know you're hurt.
你很疑惑
You're confused.
你在应对你的遗弃情结
You're dealing with abandonment issues.
还有很多问题需要解决
There's a lot to break through here.
这还需要点时间
This could take some time.
告诉我
Tell me...
弗兰斯科有没有看过你治疗的过程
did Francisco ever observe you during your sessions?
没有  他都在外面等着  怎么了
No. He waited outside. Why?
没什么
No reason.
根据他的手机显示
According to his phone,
这里是昨天弗兰斯科在选秀开始之前
this is the place Francisco went yesterday
去的地方
before the dog show.
也许是和他的赌博联系人见面
Maybe it was to meet his gambling contacts.
不能在电话里解决吗
Couldn't he just do this over the phone?
要是他被窃听了的话就不行
Not if he was being bugged.
记得弗兰斯科口袋里还有样什么东西吗
Remember what else Francisco had in his pocket?
这是什么地方
What is this place?
看上去像是个狗舍
It looks like some kind of a kennel.
是的  我看到了笼子
Yeah, I see the... cages.
但是  怎么没有
But where are the...
看门狗
shepherds.
听好了
Okay, listen,
我的一个朋友以前养过一只这个
a friend of mine had one of these.
他们能闻出恐惧
They smell fear.
所以不要害怕
So don't flinch.
无论如何  都不要
Whatever you do, don't...
跑
Run!
快点跑
Let's go!
贝克特  快跑
Beckett, go! Move!
快
Come on!
好了
Okay.
你们到我的仓库来干什么
What the hell are you doing in my warehouse?!
贝克特探长
Detectives Beckett
这是埃斯波西托警探  纽约警局
and Esposito, NYPD.
你们有搜查令吗
You got a warrant?
你是谁
Who are you?
杰克·帕特森  我为弗兰斯科·普拉尔工作
Jack Patterson. I work for Francisco Pilar.
至少他死前是  你们想要什么
Did anyway. What do you want?
我们在调查他的凶杀案
We're investigating his murder.
这里到底是什么地方
What the hell is this place?
弗兰斯科正在饲养一个新的狗品种
Francisco was breeding a new type of designer dog--
普拉尔寻回犬
the Pilar Retriever.
我在他不在的时候管理这里的运作
I managed the operation when he was traveling.
真是个悲剧
It's a real tragedy.
那家伙一辈子都用在研发新的狗品种上了
Guy spends his whole life developing a dog.
他本来都要把结果公之于众了
He was almost ready to unveil it, too.
你有多了解弗兰斯科
How well did you know Francisco?
是的  他有没有赌博的癖好
Yeah, did he have a gambling hobby,
他有没有可能从不该惹的人手里收了贿赂
Possibly took some bribes from the wrong people?
弗兰斯科没有任何癖好
Francisco didn't have hobbies.
他把一生的心血都献给了工作
His whole life was his work,
诚实的工作
and it was honest work.
好吧  事情是这样的
Yeah, well, the thing is,
弗兰斯科往一个账号里存了好几大笔钱
Francisco made a bunch of major cash deposits into an account.
让我猜猜  一次一万  是不是
Let me guess. 10 grand each, right?
普拉尔寻回犬的消息走漏了出去
Word was leaking out about the Pilar Retriever.
人们会在选秀上找到弗兰斯科
People were stopping Francisco at dog shows,
给他现金  就为了预订一只首窝的小狗
giving him cash just to reserve a pup from the first litter.
你知道他昨天为什么要赶过来吗
Any idea why he rushed over here yesterday?
事实上是的
Actually, yeah.
他带着一个窃听器扫描仪到这里来到处检查
He showed up with a bug detector and started sweeping the place.
为什么有人要监视一个狗舍呢
Why would anyone want to put a kennel under surveillance?
我不知道
I don't know.
其实他的饲养和训练方法
Well, his breeding and training methods
都是高级机密
were closely guarded secrets,
而普拉尔寻回犬让他的对手们
and the Pilar Retriever was making his competitors
非常紧张
very nervous.
有什么具体的人吗
Anyone specific?
那时听上去有点疯狂
It sounded crazy at the time,
但他认为一位托他训狗的客户在和
but he thought one of his dog training clients was in business
一个试图渗透我们生意的人做交易
with someone who was trying to infiltrate our operation.
他跟你说是哪位客户了吗
And did he tell you which client?
凯·卡普奇诺
Kay Cappuccio?
她为什么要窃取弗兰斯科的秘方
Why would she steal Francisco's secrets?
我们不能肯定她确实这么做了
Well, we don't know for sure that she did.
实际上  我们不知道他是不是真被人窃听
In fact, we don't know that he was actually bugged by anyone.
我们现在知道了
Well, we do now.
弗兰斯科的扫描仪是有储存器的
Francisco's sweeper has a memory,
它昨天早晨曾发现过监听设备
and it tripped to a listening device yesterday morning.
那是他去找凯的人
The same time he confronted Kay's people
问她在为谁卖命的时间段
and asked who she was working for.
这不会只是巧合
This can't be a coincidence.
这一切都发生在他被杀当日
It all happened on the same day he was killed.
知道吗  我觉得凯·卡普奇诺知道的
You know, I got a feeling that Kay Cappuccio
比她说出来的要多
knows a lot more than she's letting on.
我们还得找她谈谈
We're gonna have to talk to her again.
这一次...
And this time...
她得来我们这儿
She's coming to us.
卡普奇诺小姐  这边走
Right this way, Ms. Cappuccio.
你们留步
Just her.
我其实不看真人秀节目  卡普奇诺小姐
I don't really watch reality television, Ms. Cappuccio.
你想知道那是为什么吗
Would you like to know why?
想亲亲吗
You want kisses?
亲亲
Kisses.
因为我通常发现节目不全是真的
Because I usually find that it's not all that real.
而我不喜欢把故事当做
And I don't like things or people
真事呈现的人或节目
who present fiction as truth.
实际上  我觉得那就是浪费时间
In fact, I find it to be a waste of time.
好吧  你叫我来就是为了这个吗
OKay, is this why you brought me down here,
侮辱我的节目
to insult my show?
不是为了你的节目
This isn't about your show.
我想知道你跟弗兰斯科到底发生了什么事
I want to know what really happened with Francisco.
这次讲真话
This time, the truth.
我跟你说的就是真话
I told you the truth.
你的助理说
Well, according to your assistant,
弗兰斯科问你你在为谁卖命
Francisco asked you who you were working for.
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
我说了  我不知道
I told you, I have no idea.
真的吗
Really?
完全不知道他正在建立一家育狗机构
No idea that he was starting a breeding venture
而他的竞争对手急切地想了解此事
that his competitors were just dying to know about?
告诉我  "商业间谍"这个词
Tell me, does the phrase "corporate espionage"
你了解吗
mean anything to you?
不
No.
说真的  我不知道那是什么意思
No, seriously. I have no idea what it means.
能跟你们谈一下吗
Could I, uh, see you guys for a second?
扫描仪对她有反应
She set off the sweeper.
什么
What?
刚刚窃听器扫描仪就放在我桌上
The bug sweeper was on my desk.
她走过的时候  扫描仪响了
When she walked by, it went off.
你认为她身上有窃听器吗
You think she's wearing a wire?
哥们  你看看她穿的衣服
Dude, look at that outfit.
她要往哪放窃听器啊
Where is she gonna put a wire?
如果我发挥想象力  我会猜...
Well, if I had to be creative, I'd guess--
我只是夸张而已
That's rhetorical.
我们去技术室
We went into the tech room
分离窃听器发送信号的频率
to isolate the frequency that the bug was transmitting on,
我们发现了...
and we found, uh, well...
给他们看看
Show 'em.
好吧
All right.
好宝宝
Oh, sweet baby.
妈妈马上就送你回家
Mommy's gonna get you home so soon.
胸部
Boobs?
可不是一般的胸  是她的胸
Not just any boobs, her boobs.
放在狗项圈上了
It's on the collar.
狗的项圈的其中一块宝石里面有摄像头
There's a camera in one of the jewels in the dog's collar.
你说她无论去哪都带着她的狗
You said she takes that dog with her wherever she goes?
就是说弗兰斯科
Which means that Francisco
可能不是受到监控的对象
probably wasn't the intended target of the surveillance.
凯·卡普奇诺才是
Kay Cappuccio is.
真不敢相信有人一直在监视我
I cannot believe that someone has been watching me.
卡普奇诺小姐  你说你的狗
Ms. Cappuccio, when you say that your dog
你去哪都会带上
goes with you everywhere--
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
他可能看到了我出浴
He could've seen me in the shower.
他可能看到了我和雷吉在床上
He could have seen me and Reggie in bed together.
他可能看到了我没化妆的样子
He could've seen me without my makeup.
我觉得好受侵犯
I feel so violated.
听我说  狗仔队虽然咄咄逼人
Look, the paparazzi are aggressive,
但是在狗项圈上装监视器
but wiring a dog collar,
这可要费不少功夫啊
that's a lot of effort to go through
就为拿到明星录影带吗
just to get some celebrity video.
可是  这可不是一般的明星录影带啊
Oh, well, I mean, it's not just any celebrity video.
美国名人消息网  悬赏好像有一百万
I mean, T.M.Z.'s offered, like, a million bucks
要买我的首张裸照
for the first naked picture of me.
要我说  这数目还太低呢
You ask me, that number's on the low side.
你嘴真是太甜了
You are too sweet.
谢谢
Thank you.
一百万可是很强大的动机
A million dollars is a pretty powerful incentive.
是啊
Yeah.
你什么时候买的那个项圈
When did you get that collar?
几周前
Um, a few weeks ago.
摄像头只能是那之后安装上的
The camera would've had to be installed since then,
就是说安装的人能接触到你的狗
which would mean they would need access to your dog.
洛丽塔几乎与我寸步不离
Lolita is barely ever out of my sight.
除了她出去散步
Only when she goes on her walk
或者去做动物美容时
or to the groomer's.
好吧  我们需要所有那些人的名字
Okay, we're gonna need the names of all of those people
还有你家里的雇员名单
along with your house staff.
我们需要对他们所有人做背景调查
We're gonna want to run background checks on all of them.
在此期间  我们该让摄像头继续工作
In the meantime, we should keep the collar-cam active.
我们可不想让幕后黑手知道我们查到他们身上了
We don't want whoever's behind this to know we're on to them.
没错  所以你该做什么还做什么
Right, which means, just go about your regular routine.
就尽量把你的隐私
Just try to keep your private moments...
保护好
more private.
如果凯才是真正的监控对象
Look, if Kay was the actual target of the surveillance,
这一切又跟弗兰斯科的被杀有什么关系呢
What does any of this have to do with Francisco's murder?
如果...
What if...
弗兰斯科发现了项圈被动过手脚
Francisco discovers the collar is rigged,
他把狗还给了凯  但他当时
He returns the dog to Kay, but doesn't get a chance
没来得及与她对质
to confront her about it at the time,
但是那个在监控这着画面的人
but whoever's monitoring the feed
本想看到她一丝不挂的样子
hoping to see her naked
却听到凯说选秀结束后她要去跟
hears Kay say that she intends to talk to Francisco
弗兰斯科谈谈
after the show?
所以他们为了封口而杀人吗
So then they killed him to keep him quiet?
我们是在说狗仔队
Well, this is paparazzi we're talking about.
我觉得那些人渣为了一笔大钱而动杀机不无可能
I could see one of those scum killing for a fat paycheck.
那么我们如果能找出给项圈装监视器的人
So if we find whoever bugged that collar,
或许就能找到凶手
then we might be able to find our killer.
我们可以翻看一下凯最近的照片
Well, we could go through recent photos of Kay,
就是刊登在小报  八卦网站上的照片
you know, from tabloids, gossip web sites,
看看她能不能认出哪张
and see if she can identify any of them
是项圈摄像头拍下来的
as being from the collar-cam.
那样或许能顺藤摸瓜
And then there might be a trail
找到安摄像头的人
that leads back to the guilty party.
那么我们得找个人
So we're gonna have to find somebody
-去把照片翻出来  -我去吧
- to pull all those photos- - I'll do it.
埃斯波西托  你是情窦初开了吗
Got a little case of, uh, puppy love there, Esposito?
你知道她有个很正式的男友吧
You do realize that she's got a serious boyfriend, right?
谁  雷吉吗
Who... Reggie?
他就是健身操录影带里的替补舞者
He was a back-up dancer in a fitness video.
我是说  我都不知道
I mean, I don't even know
她跟那种蠢蛋在一起干嘛
what she's doing with that knucklehead.
算了
No.
看来埃斯波西托
Aw. Looks like Esposito...
不是分局里唯一受挫的
isn't the only frustrated dog in the precinct.
谁把他锁在里面了
Who closed him up in there?
他得睡一觉
Oh, he needed to take a nap,
但他不能在这儿过夜
but he can't stay there overnight.
我可能带他回我家
I could take him home with me.
阿丽克西斯这周末不在  我正好缺个伴儿
Alexis is gone for the weekend, and I could use the company.
要不  我也可以带他回家啊
Or... I could take him home.
我在考虑养狗的事
I mean, I've been thinking about getting a dog.
这或许正是试一下的好机会
This might be a great chance at a trial run.
好吧  那我想你可以带他回家
Yeah. All right. Then I guess you can take him.
我是说...
I mean, I--
我是说我不想让你感觉孤苦伶仃的
I mean, I don't--I don't want you to feel lonely.
可以掷硬币
I could flip for it.
不玩石头剪子布吗
No Roshambo?
那样对你不公平啊
Well, I mean, that would put you at an unfair disadvantage.
我这么厉害
I'm pretty good--
-来吧  卡塞尔  来吧  -好吧
- Oh, come on, Castle. Let's go. - All right.
你要知道  玩这个是有策略的
Just so you know, there's strategies in this game that, uh...
-三局两胜  -好
- Two out of three? - Mm-hmm.
五局三胜
Three out of five?
行
Sure.
这事我们还有另一种解决方案
You know, there is another way that we can go about this.
卡塞尔  你该在一个小时前送它来的
Castle, you were supposed to be here over an hour ago.
我们这是"共享"监护
It's called "shared" custody,
不是"想出现就出现"监护
not "show up when you want" custody.
话是没错  我原本以为东西带全了
Yeah, I thought I had everything together,
但是最后一刻我才发现找不到呱呱叫先生了
but at the last minute, I could not find Mr. Squeaky.
别担心要喂它什么
So don't worry about feeding him.
我喂了它一块没吃完的牛腓利
I had a rib eye I couldn't finish.
你给它吃牛排
You fed him a steak?
是啊  别担心  我们饭后运动了
Yeah. Don't worry. We worked it off.
它在客厅玩了扔玩具
He played, uh, fetch in the hall,
然后我们还一起看了《比佛利拜金狗》
and then we watched some "Beverly Hills Chihuahua."
天啊  这家伙
Boy, this guy--
这家伙超爱抱抱
This guy is a snuggler.
我敢说你让它坐在沙发上了  是吗
And I bet you let him sit on your couch, didn't you?
不要紧  你做了有趣搞怪的一方
No, it's okay. You can be the fun one.
我就做严厉刻板的一方
I'll just be the bad guy,
因为你绝对不可以把我的沙发
because there is no way that you are shedding
弄得都是毛
all over my couch.
没关系  他待在那里也很舒服
Oh, no. He's perfectly happy right there.
还有它最喜欢你轻揉它双眼之间
Oh, and he loves it when you rub him right between the eyes.
用大拇指轻轻绕圈  像这样
Just little circles with your thumb, just like this.
不要太用力  只要
Not too hard, just...
-卡塞尔  -就这样  你懂的
- Castle-- - Yeah, there's... you get it.
好了  好了
Yeah. Um, all right.
你们玩得开心点
You guys have fun.
别太想我哦
Don't miss me too much.
我跟它说  不是你
The dog, not you.
好吧  上来
Okay, come on.
过来
Right here.
来吧  来吧
Come on. Right here.
好啦  你太可爱了
Come on. You're so cute.
我从没想过我会这么说
I never thought I would say this,
但是我现在真是看够我自己了
but I am so sick of looking at myself right now.
我都没法想象你的感受
I can't even imagine how you must feel.
别担心我
Don't worry about me.
那么
What about...
那张呢
that one?
那是我周四穿的
Um, that is what I wore on Thursday.
也就是说洛丽塔在清洗店  所以  不是
So that means Lolita was off at the Groomer's, so, no.
这张照片不可能是从项圈的摄像机拍的
The collar couldn't have taken this picture.
我真不敢相信你只从
I can't believe you can identify
穿着的衣服就能分辨那是哪一天
what day of the year it is just from what you're wearing.
而大家偏偏说我没有才华
And people say I'm talentless.
别理会那些心存愤恨的人
Don't listen to those haters.
他们有多少人能说他们有自己的化妆品品牌
How many of them can say they got their own cosmetics line, huh?
这张呢
How about this one?
哦不  上帝啊  我记得那天
No. God. I remember that day.
有个怪吓人的摄影师
There was this creep photographer
藏在两辆车中间
hidden down between two cars.
这真让人抑郁
This is depressing.
别担心  我们会抓住这家伙的
Don't worry. We'll catch the guy.
不是  我是说我的生活  就是
No, I mean, my life. It's...
购物
shopping
开派对  再购物
and partying and more shopping.
人们争着拍我做着这些蠢事
And it is bad enough that people fight to take pictures of me
就已经够糟糕了  但是
doing all this dumb stuff, but...
你真的觉得弗兰斯科
Do you really think that Francisco
是因为这个才被谋杀的吗
was murdered because of it?
就算是
Well, if he was,
也不是你的错
it doesn't make it your fault.
他有家人吗
Did he have a family?
没有
No.
他和狗相依为命
It was just him and his dog.
那样  我想我们没什么区别
Oh, well, I guess we weren't so different then.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你  你有雷吉
You, uh, well, you have... Reggie,
菲比  还有很多朋友
Phoebe, all your friends.
看看这些照片
Look at all these pictures.
你从未落单
You're never alone.
照片真的很能骗人
Pictures can be really deceiving.
等等
Wait.
-这张  -这张
- This one. - This one?
这是从高角度拍的
It's from a high angle.
不不  这是上周拍的
No, no, this is from last week.
这天洛丽塔没栓皮带
This is the day that Lolita got off her leash,
她爬上了这座山
and she climbed up this hill,
她可能刚好在这个高点
and this would've been her exact vantage point.
现在我只要打给《明星特报》
Now all I gotta do is call "Celebrity Report,"
通过他们应该可以助我找到...
and they oughta lead me right to...
马库斯·怀特
Marcus Hiatt.
所有被确认是从项圈摄像机拍摄的照片
All the pictures IDed from the collar-cam
都能反查到他身上
can be traced back to him.
他和其他狗仔队一起守在凯家门外
He was outside Kay's place with the rest of the paparazzi.
他可是个变态跟踪狗仔
The guy's a full-on stalkerazzi.
骚扰  非法入侵  甚至是破门而入
Harassment, trespassing, even B&E--
看起来这家伙为了获得高价照片
Seems like there's nothing this guy won't do
会不惜一切代价
to get that big-money shot.
而且我们知道他有犯案的机会
And we know he had opportunity for the murder
因为他也被派去拍摄狗狗选秀
because he was issued credentials to that Dog Show.
不用猜也知道他现在在哪
Wonder where he might be now.
谁是你的有线供应商
Who is your cable service provider?
因为我收不到这个频道
Because I do not get this channel.
出来
Come here.
认出你的作品了吗  马库斯
You recognize your work, Marcus?
凯·卡普奇诺认出了  买你照片那个人也认出了
Kay Cappuccio did, and so did that Scandal Rag you sold it to.
你怎么接近那条狗的
How'd you get access to the dog?
你收买别人了吗
Did you pay someone off?
你们推测的太不靠谱了
You guys are way off base here, all right?
听着  和你们想的不一样
Look, it's not what you think.
不是吗  因为我认为你知道
No? 'Cause I think you knew
如果弗兰斯科告诉凯项圈的事情
that if Francisco told Kay about the collar,
她会直接去找联邦调查局
she'd go straight to the FBI.
你的一切就玩完了
And you saw your whole world crashing down around you.
我没杀弗兰斯科那家伙
I did not kill that Francisco guy.
狗项圈上的摄像机也不是我装的
And I didn't even wire that dog collar either.
马库斯  我们刚刚抓到你...
Marcus, we just caught you...
谁是好孩子啊
Who's a good boy, huh?
谁是好孩子啊  马库斯是好孩子吗
Who's a good boy? Is Marcus a good boy?
不  他不是好孩子
No, he's not a good boy.
他是坏孩子
He's a bad boy.
黑进她的手机
...hacked into her cell phone,
也许  找些裸照什么的
maybe, uh, find some nude pictures of her or something.
但是不知怎么回事  我搜到了那视频信号
But then outta nowhere, I pick up that video feed--
凯·卡普奇诺脱下浴袍
Kay Cappuccio dropping her bathrobe
开始淋浴
and jumping in to the shower.
我知道他们说她没才华
Look, I know they say she's got no talent,
但是我得说  兄弟
but let me tell you something, brother,
那妞的"才华"比
that girl's got more talent than a--
你  说话注意点
Hey! Watch your mouth.
你真的以为我们会相信
Do you actually expect us to believe
你是无意间搜到那信号吗
that you accidentally came across that feed?
我都不知道信号从哪发出来
Look, I didn't know where it was coming from,
说真的  我不在乎
and really, I didn't care.
我是捡了下金蛋的鸡
I was sitting on a gold mine,
只是一开始我没有录制的设备
only I didn't have the equipment to record it at first.
所以我急忙弄好了一个
So I scrambled to get it set up,
但是那天晚些时候  他们把那狗
but later that day, they shipped the dog off
送给了那个该死的训练师
to that damn trainer.
这故事不错  马库斯
Well, that's a great story, Marcus.
听着
Look...
如果你们想找出谁杀了他
If you want to find who killed him,
那就查清他和谁在做生意
find who he's doing business with.
我指的不是他那训练狗的生意
And I'm not talking about his dog training business either.
那你指的是什么
Then what are you talking about?
我开回去去检查信号
I drove back there to check on the signal, all right?
想着也许我能搞清
Thought maybe I could find out
狗什么时候会送回到凯那里
when the dog was going back to Kay.
知道我听到弗兰斯科在谈论什么吗
The things I heard that Francisco guy talking about?
他可是搞了些不正经的东西
Yeah, he was into some sketchy stuff.
真的吗  兄弟
Really, bro?
你好意思坐在这说别人不正经
You're gonna sit here and call someone else sketchy?
听我说完好吗
Listen to what I'm saying, all right?
他说有阿根廷来的货物
The guy was talking about shipments from Argentina,
蒙混过关
getting past customs,
黑市价
street values.
是毒品吗
Drugs?
是啊  符合他的旅行路线
Yeah, it seems to fit his travel.
除国际旅行外
In addition to his international trips,
大多都是去波士顿  新奥尔良  西雅图
made a lot of flights to Boston, New Orleans, Seattle,
长滩  迈阿密
Long Beach, Miami.
-全是港口城市  -对
- All port cities. - Exactly.
飞往世界各地给狗秀当评委
The international travel to judge dog shows--
真是完美的掩护
that's a perfect cover.
这么说狗训练师是个毒品快递员
So our dog trainer is a drug courier.
难怪他疑神疑鬼担心被监听
No wonder he was so paranoid about being bugged.
那我们那天看到的仓库是...
Then that warehouse that we saw...
配种基地个屁
Breeding facility, my ass.
普拉尔寻回犬
The Pilar retriever?
编的不错  不是吗
Pretty good story, right?
我总得想办法把你们赶出去
Hey, I had to get you outta there somehow.
帕特森先生  恐怕你还不明白
Mr. Patterson, I don't think you understand
事情的严重性
how serious this is.
我们正在申请搜查令
We're in the process of obtaining a warrant.
会把仓库搜个底朝天
We're gonna search that warehouse from top to bottom.
我们很清楚
And we got a pretty good idea
能在那找到什么
of what we're gonna find in there.
我来告诉你们能找到什么
Well, I'll tell you exactly what you'll find--
为躲过海关而特制的
Suitcases with false bottoms
活底手提箱
for smuggling drugs through customs,
两千克的纯阿根廷海洛因
about 2 kilos of pure Argentinean heroin.
前所未见的最优秀的缉毒犬
And the best drug-sniffing dogs we've ever had.
我不叫卡克·帕特森
My name's not Kack Patterson.
我是肯尼·维泽尔  美国海关探员
Kenny Weizer. U.S. Customs agent.
你们这有咖啡吗
You got any coffee?
这么说弗兰斯科是在训练缉毒犬
So Francisco was training drug-sniffing dogs?
他手段太高明了
His methods were amazing.
不管我们认为货运到哪
Personally handled deployment
他都亲自部署调度
wherever we thought the shipment was coming in.
这就解释了去港口城市的旅行
Which explains all that travel to those port cities,
那些收入  遮遮掩掩
and the payments, and the secrecy.
很抱歉在仓库时没跟你们坦白
Yeah, sorry about giving you the runaround at the warehouse,
但当你跟贩毒集团打交道时
but when you're dealing with the cartels,
你不得不加倍小心
you can't be too careful.
所以你供出凯·卡普奇诺
Oh, so that's why you gave us Kay Cappuccio's name,
你以为是她监听弗兰斯科
because you thought she bugged Francisco.
不挑明我们对瓦奎斯业务的意图
Yeah, we couldn't really launch an investigation
我们是无法展开调查的
without tipping our hand to the Vasquez operation.
所以我想  我告诉你们我所掌握的
So I figured, I'd tell you what I know,
看你们能查到些什么
see where you could get.
瓦奎斯  是阿根廷的贩毒集团对吗
Vasquez--that's out of Argentina, right?
一个庞大的走私海洛因的家族
That's a huge heroin smuggling family.
维泽尔探员
Agent Weizer,
弗兰斯科的狗嗅到毒品时
what are Francisco's dogs trained to do
会有什么反应
when they smell drugs?
它们会猛抓地板  怎么了
They paw at the ground. Why?
罗亚尔就是这种反应
Because that's what Royal was doing.
所以我想狗治疗师是对的
So I guess that dog therapist was right.
它想告诉我们一些事
He was trying to tell us something.
它在凶手身上嗅到了毒品的味道
He smelled drugs on our killer.
那说得通   瓦奎斯贩毒集团
Well, that makes sense. The Vasquez cartel had
从弗兰斯科的死中获益匪浅
a hell of a lot to gain from Francisco's death.
他训练出的缉毒犬  导致货物被查
His program was costing them a fortune
损失了很多钱
in intercepted shipments.
这就是他们监视监听弗兰斯科的原因
Which is why they wanted eyes and ears on Francisco.
他们想知道海关稽查是怎么进行的
They wanted to figure out how the customs' operation worked.
但当弗兰斯科意识到他被监听后
But once Francisco realized he was under surveillance,
他们知道自己暴露了
they knew he was on to them.
所以他们找人干掉他
So they got someone to finish him off.
可能就是在凯·卡普奇诺的狗颈圈上
Probably the same person
装监视器的那个人
who wired Kay Cappuccio's dog collar.
要想在狗颈圈上装监视器
Whoever wired up that dog collar
必须具备三个条件
had to have three things.
首先  能够接触到狗
One--access to the dog.
其次  知晓弗兰斯科会训练那只狗
Two--knowledge that Francisco would be training that dog.
第三  与瓦奎斯贩毒集团有某种关联
Three--some connection to the Vasquez cartel.
凶手就藏在
The intersection of these three circles
三个圈圈重合之处
holds the identity of our killer.
它又抓地板了
He's doing that thing again.
是啊  可我身上没海洛因啊  卡塞尔
Yeah, but I don't have any heroin on me, Castle.
但它为何会那样呢  除非
Well, why would he react like that unless...
贝克特  你搽香水了吗
Beckett, are you wearing perfume?
为了给以后做参考  我偏爱"喧嚣"
And just for future reference, I am partial to Fracas.
别臭美了
Listen, don't flatter yourself, okay?
我只是喷了点
I just spritzed some of this stuff
凯送的礼物篮里的香水
that Kay sent over in the gift basket.
它为什么会对香水有反应
Why would he react to that?
因为主要成分是婴栗花的提炼物
Because the main ingredient is essence of poppy flower.
海洛因是由吗啡提炼的
And heroin is made from morphine,
而吗啡又取自婴栗
which comes from the opium poppy.
假设在凶案现场
Guys, what if, at the crime scene,
令它有反应的不是毒品
he was pawing not at drugs,
而是香水的香味
but at the scent of that perfume.
有可能  但这款香水还未上市
Yeah, but this perfume hasn't even come out yet.
谁会搽这款香水呢
I mean, who would be wearing it?
就一个人
Only one person.
-不会是凯  -可她的确在凶案现场出现过
- Not kay. - Well, she was at the crime scene.
卡塞尔  我们现在谈的可不是狗仔  名人
Castle, we're not talking about paparazzi and celebrities.
我们说的是一个贩毒集团
We're dealing with a drug cartel.
好  那我们回忆下要找的疑犯特征
Okay, well, let's remember what we're looking for.
首先  能够接触到狗  打勾
One--access to the dog. Check.
其次  知晓弗兰斯科会训练那只狗  打勾
Two--knowledge that Francisco was training the dog. Check.
就是不确定跟贩毒集团是否有联系
Only thing we're missing is a connection to the cartel.
我想我找到两者间的联系了
Uh, guys, I think I might have our link.
凯·卡普奇诺六个月前在阿根廷拍了广告
Kay Cappuccio shot a commercial in Argentina six months ago.
那又如何
So?
阿根廷那么大
Argentina's a big country.
这不能说明她和瓦奎斯家族有联系
It doesn't mean that she's connected to the Vasquez family.
但是我下面说的能
But this does.
她住在朱尼尔·瓦奎斯家里
She stayed at the compound of Junior Vasquez,
贩毒集团的首席副官
first lieutenant of the cartel.
她就是凶手
She's the one.
我只想和我所有的粉丝们问声好
I just wanna say hi to all my fans out there.
打个招呼  洛丽塔
Say hi, Lolita.
我想提醒大家下个月  我的新香水
And I want to remind you guys that my new scent,
就要上市了
hits stores next month.
凯·卡普奇诺之罪恶的欢愉
Kay Cappuccio's guilty pleasure--
确保他的罪名是渴望得到你
make sure he's guilty of wanting you.
罪恶的欢愉
Guilty pleasure
还是只有罪恶
or just guilty?
这段录像和案子有什么关系
What does this video have to do with anything?
录像拍摄完十五分钟  你去后台
This was about 15 minutes before you went backstage
到了弗兰斯科·普拉尔的化妆间
to Francisco Pilar's dressing room.
所以呢
So?
我们有理由怀疑
So we have reason to suspect
凶手搽了你的香水
that our killer was wearing your perfume.
那不可能  它还没上市
Well, that's impossible. It wasn't even out yet.
唯一搽那香水的人是我
I'm the only person that had it.
她有意识到自己变相认罪了吗
Does she realize she just incriminated herself?
我说过她人很好  没说她聪明
I said she was nice. I didn't say anything about smart.
海关署维泽尔探员来电
Customs Agent Weizer's on the phone
找埃斯波西托警探
for Detective Esposito.
有劳
Thanks.
他找你有事吗
What was that about?
我告诉他  找到任何证明
I asked him to call me if he found
凯·卡普奇诺与瓦奎斯家族有关的证据就通知我
any definitive Kay Cappuccio connection to the Vasquez family.
你知道他们什么时候结束吗
You know when they're gonna be done in there?
有个《名利场》的记者
We got a reporter from "Vanity fair"
待会要来家里做访问
coming by the house later.
他们让她做封面人物
They're giving her the cover.
我不清楚  兄弟
I don't know, bro.
但是  祝你们访问顺利
But, um, good luck with that.
埃斯波西托
Esposito.
你跟朱尼尔·瓦奎斯是什么关系
What's your relationship with Junior Vasquez?
朱尼尔  他真是个甜心
Junior? He is such a sweetheart.
他们阿根廷有《追随卡普奇诺》
Um, they have "Keeping Up With Cappuccio"
他是个超级粉丝
in Argentina, so he's kind of a big fan.
你知道瓦奎斯家族是
Do you realize that the Vasquez family
南美头号海洛因出口商吗
is the number one heroin exporter in South America?
什么
What?
天啊  伙计们  我不知道啊
Oh, my god. You guys, I did not know that.
失陪
Excuse me.
等我一会儿  卡塞尔
Give me a minute, Castle.
这真是噩梦
This is a nightmare.
海洛因  谋杀
Heroin, murder--
真希望我从来都没听说过弗兰斯科
I just wish I had never even heard of Francisco.
凯  你...
Kay, how...
你是怎么知道他这个人的
How did you hear about him?
通过雷吉
Reggie.
他在杂志之类的东西里看到他
He read about him in, like, a magazine or something.
他说他是最棒的  他坚持让我雇佣他
He said he was the best, so he insisted I use him.
那让洛丽塔
So it was Reggie's idea
去弗兰斯科那训练也是雷吉的主意吗
that Lolita go to Francisco for training?
是啊
Yeah.
确保他的罪名是渴望得到你
Make sure he's guilty of wanting you.
嗨  宝贝
Hi, baby.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
确定
Positive.
海关的确是把凯和瓦奎斯联系起来了
Customs connected Kay to the Vasquez family all right,
是通过雷吉
through Reggie.
原来他跟瓦奎斯的孩子上同一所学校
Turns out he went to school with one of the Vasquez kids.
他才是关联  不是凯
He's the connection, not Kay.
小心
Look out!
搞定他  罗亚尔
Get him, Royal.
他对全部罪行供认不讳
So he confessed to the whole thing.
瓦奎斯贩毒集团怀疑弗兰斯科
The Vasquez cartel suspected that Francisco
为海关训练狗狗
was training dogs for customs.
而当凯需要训练洛丽塔的时候
And then when Kay needed Lolita trained,
雷吉将她引向弗兰斯科
Reggie steered her towards Francisco
然后在狗项圈上安了摄像头
and then wired the dog collar.
但这事被弗兰斯科发现  雷吉就慌了
But Francisco caught on, and Reggie panicked.
他觉得自己必须保护贩毒集团
He felt he had to protect the cartel.
雷吉想要在贩毒集团面前好好表现
Yeah, and Reggie wanted to get in good with the cartel.
他知道他在凯这吃软饭的日子
He knew that his days of mooching off of kay
要到头了  尽管媒体在报道
were almost over, in spite of all the reports
她俩要结婚
that the two of them were getting married.
等等  你是说...小报报道错了
Whoa, whoa. You mean... the tabloids were wrong?
是的
Yeah, and, um,
还有一件事我也想错了
you know, I was wrong about something, too.
分局有个吉祥物挺有用的
Turns out having a mascot in the precinct can be pretty useful.
我在想  或许今晚你带它回家
So I was thinking for tonight, maybe you take him home,
我大概在晚上九点半来接它
and then I'll swing by, pick him up, maybe 9:30?
我不确定  卡塞尔
Oh, I don't know, Castle.
我认为这种轮流制
I don't know if this whole splitting time thing
不是长久之计
is good long-term solution.
那怎么办  隔天晚上  工作日周末吗
Well, what then, alternating nights, uh, weekends/weekdays?
我想那样会把它搞糊涂的
I-I think it'll just confuse the poor guy.
是啊  它已经做了足够的心理治疗了
God knows, he's had enough therapy.
我认为它应该在一个住处安家
I think he deserves one home.
我明白怎么回事了
Oh, I see where this is going.
不  不是石子剪刀布
Uh, no. No, no roshambo.
有更好的主意吗
You got a better idea?
我认为应该由罗亚尔来决定
I think we should let Royal decide.
我们分别站在房间的两头
We go to opposite ends of the room,
它走向谁  就住谁家
and wherever he goes, that's home.
好嘞
Let's do it.
坐下
Sit down.
坐下  好孩子  别动
Sit down. Good boy. Stay there.
坐好
Stay there.
好了
All right.
准备好了吗
Ready?
准备好了
Ready.
过来  小子
Come here, boy.
-到我这来  罗亚尔  -过来  罗亚尔
- Come over here, Royal. Come on. - Come here, Royal.
过来
Come right here.
-这是个重大的决定  -罗亚尔  谁最爱你
- It's a big decision... - Royal, who loves you?
-但我知道你会做出正确的选择  -过来  罗亚尔
- But I know you'll make the right one. - Come on, royal. Come on.
我的沙发超级舒服
My couch is super comfortable.
-过来啊  罗亚尔大宝贝  -过来  伙计
- Royal, come right over here, baby. - Come on, buddy.
-你知道在你心底  -过来啊  罗亚尔
- You know in your heart. - Come over here. Come on, royal.
-你是男人的挚友  -谁在那  过来啊
- Man's best friend. - Who's here? Come over here.
男人哦
Man's.
看来它做出决定了
Looks like he's made his choice,
是我
and it's me.
你真有品味  罗亚尔
You have such good taste, Royal.
嘿  伙计
Hi, buddy.
你真有品味
You have every good taste.
-你好啊  -你确定要收留它吗
- Hi, buddy. - Are you sure you want to take him?
或许我们应该来个三局两胜
Yeah, maybe we should do two out of three.
我和洛丽塔需要一个强壮的男性在家
Oh, yes, Lolita and I need a big strong man around the house,
尤其是像它这么忠诚的
Especially one as loyal as this,
对不对
right, bud?
罗亚尔  你正式加入卡普奇诺家了
Royal, you are officially a Cappuccio now.
你一直都很贴心
And you have been so sweet.
呃  那个  我知道狗仔队有时
Hey, if--you know, I know that the paparazzi can be
很恶劣  如果你有需要
very vicious sometimes, so if you ever need anything,
我是说任何事
like, I mean anything at all,
你知道到哪里找我
You know where to find me.
总有一天我会让你履行承诺的
I just might take you up on that one day.
你知道吗  这也许是最好的解决办法
Well, you know what? I mean, I'm sure it's for the best.
它在我家会很寂寞的
He woulda been lonely at my place.
没人跟它玩
There's nobody to play with.
是啊  我家也是
Yeah, mine, too.
它们倒是挺喜欢对方的
They do look like they enjoy each other.
亲爱的
Hey, sweetheart.
旅途如何
How was your trip?
挺有趣  想我了吗
We had fun. Miss me?
非常想
Ah, terribly.
但是在没有你的情况下  我也过得不错
But I did manage to have a good time without you
跟我的新朋友大狗罗亚尔
with my new friend Royal the dog.
你买了一条狗吗
You got a dog?
没有  但是我照顾它了一段时间
No, but I was looking after him for a while,
之后我就琢磨
but it made me think.
你小时候
All those times when you were little,
总是求我养条狗  我拒绝是因为
how you begged me for a dog, and I refused because--
你说  最后总是要你来喂它
You said, you'd be the one who'd wind up having to feed it,
而每天你能记得喂我就已经够难的了
and it was hard enough remembering to feed me every day.
是啊  咦  最后那句我不记得了
Yeah, I... I don't remember that last part.
潜台词哦
It was subtext.
有那么一点这个意思
Barely.
总之呢  我想要补偿你
Anyway, I want to make it up to you.
我要给你买条狗
I want to get you a dog.
唯一的问题是  你想要哪种
Only question is, what kind of dog do we get?
起什么名字  在哪间房睡觉
What are we gonna name it? Whose room is it gonna sleep--
老爸  别急
Whoa, dad, slow down.
我要去上大学了  记得吗
I'm leaving for college soon, remember?
而宿舍是不让养狗的
You can't have a dog in your dorm room.
是哦
Right.
我知道  那我在这照顾它
Well, I know. I'll just take care of him here.
你可以随时回来看它
You can come visit him whenever you can.
那么...这条你想买的狗
So... this dog you want to get,
为我而买
you know, for me.
不会是想把我尽可能地
This wouldn't be an enticement
从大学吸引回家的引诱物吧
to come home from college more often, would it?
别假装你比我聪明
Don't pretend like you're smarter than me.
潜台词是我教你的  丫头
I taught you subtext, young lady.
别担心
Don't worry.
我会没完没了地回来
I'll come back and visit so much,
让你都受不了
you'll be sick of me.
保证吗
Promise?
保证
Yeah.
总得有人隔段时间给你搞点吃的吧[喂狗的说法]
Someone has to leave food out for you once in a while.
说到这个  我有点饿了
Speaking of, I'm kinda hungry right now.
狗饼干
Kibbles 'n bits?
用勺子吃花生酱
Peanut butter on a spoon?
中餐
Chinese.
我要吃三明治
I'd like a sandwich.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.